So today's which is going to be updated, it's totally from home, you can do it at any time from home, it's totally part
time, as much as you fear, your salary will be made, no further issue,
18 years plus Any person can do this and whether he is a retired day before tomorrow, whether he is a housewife,
whatever it is, okay and I have brought two updates and there will be no interview in this,
you will have 15 hours of training and after that there will be a test which 1995% people easily crack easily
and go to joining, then whenever I have brought in the updates, I
will put the link of both in my description box, you can see it and
apply ISP by clicking on it, then fear Let's start this video quickly but
before that if you have not subscribed to my channel then brother channel
is subscribed from gate to bank and second is to SBI life then I am going to tell both through this video that How to
apply, so first when I am going to discuss about ICC, you do not have to pay any
money for this training, but the company will provide you, in this your monthly salary
can go up to 85000, as it depends on you. That this Totally Parli is commission based, when you
get 15% commission, no matter how much day after day after day you do it, you will get 15% of that amount only
in the whole month which is your salary. 85 ja shakti hai issue policy instantly online koi paper
ko hota hota hai to anyone if you have talked on the phone then you
can execute it immediately by doing online saree thing with him Bindaas ok Totally it is from home part time when it happens that You do not have to spend any time in this,
if you are a businessman, whether you are a housewife, whether you are already a story, and when you do it, whether you are retired
day after day , there you can spend a day or two or three hours, you can decide your time and work at home.
You can do it comfortably, there is definitely a laptop piece, both are not on it, for the time I am telling, there is no need of a
laptop for both, you can comfortably do it from mobile too, okay, as
in this Your rank is going to be that of an insurance advisor and you are comfortable because
nowadays all this digital has become so strong, without paper you can easily reduce it, okay
here are written 15 s of certificate by IRDAI is ok so the Indian government has
made training of 15 questions compulsory for this and after that there is a test which is compulsory by the Indian government, which I have
told easy people qualify and take it, there is a video in which You can see okay let's
see here pay directly with ICC Lombard with that you will directly reduce okay complete
working on accessibility whatever working festival test you totally you aapne se apne bus
ho gaye koi it time ka vaar No, when you want to schedule your time back, you can do that,
ok, reliable support, you can ask these people anytime for any instant help, instant
policy, which is the way to help you totally in anything, paper In this no one will remain on timely
commission and then you will get money timely, then all these things like an example has been given and a chart has been given
in which it is written that if the insurance of tax is minimum of 25000 then 15-15 how much percent will you get?
You get these sentences, you get commission, so your salary is given on this, so it has happened before, who
can do this, like in this, when you are already doing the story in business tomorrow or
the story is break free. If you got a little time during the vacation time, you have got some break milk, then you
can reduce it, if you want to reduce the house wife, then all these things, the company is serious, even then you can do it, you are
starting an entrepreneur. When you are a student or especially for a student, it is very
good because it is clear cut that brother, you are 10th pass, only then you can do it comfortably,
so you must have at least 10th pass and 18 years plus is mandatory for both, when I am telling
you, it is a good thing, you have done it first and now let's go to the second, how to fill the SBI form,
I will tell you, there is nothing simple to do in this. Your form is written
give mobile number email id full name after daal and then after that download install earning today click dog
then after that you will be contacted mail will be sent when your training will start everything
will be mentioned in it ok in mail So these are the big ones of ICC, immediately we go to SBI Life
One of the biggest thing is that why should Unlimited Food Limited be made in this, the salary is as much as you
do, the more you fear, the more you keep the time dog, the more you keep these cents on your commission, when it becomes your commission, there is also a
scene of 15%. Be comfortable with yourself and in this your communication is like someone is
under pressure, they say yes or look at this also, don't be afraid of hearing the name of sales, your
company skills and your links are very much. It is good to improve, okay, it
is necessary to do this thing because the fear of people's mother does not come out in them, okay,
all these things are the rights of SBI life and see the application, clear cut is also written on this unaplicant
businessman distribution anyone can apply from this application minimum 18 years should be 10th pass
then in this also after your training you will have to give test and its
form is also given below Phoolka asked this city, asked the state, after that,
after entering the capture, submit your dog, after submitting it, you will directly contact and mail directly from there,
after that they will guide you, how to do what you have to do. How to fill this form of yours
must have become clear, you apply both the forms and in both, in which you
find butter, in which you feel best, then you can join in it, the right thing is that
after applying 90s in lake 95 96% people are selected ok and if you have spoken the form well you have this
communication skill you want to proof then this is the best place ok you apply in this and
learn your skills in this way daily updates It brings relief, so if you
like my channel and my hard work, please subscribe to my channel, I will like the video, if there is any doubt,
then comment, I reply to every comment, thank you, thank you for watching my video